<dialogue>
     <line>
          <speaker>
               First Mate Bartholomew
          </speaker>
          <text>
               Ah, there you are! You must be my new assistant, yes? Thank goodness! You mustn’t keep your future captain waiting… but I will forgive you just this once.
          </text>
          <responses>
               <response>
                    I’m not here to -
               </response>
          </responses>
     </line>
     <line>
          <speaker>
               First Mate Bartholomew
          </speaker>
          <text>
               Now, before I take you on as my partner, let me ask you this, ma cherie -- what makes a captain, in your view?
          </text>
          <responses>
               <response>
                    The vote of the crew?
               </response>
               <response>
                    Skilled leadership?
               </response>
               <response>
                    Not sinking the ship?
               </response>
          </responses>
     </line>
     <line>
          <speaker>
               First Mate Bartholomew
          </speaker>
          <text>
               I see... that’s quite charming, however, I’m afraid it lacks a certain appeal. You see, there is far more to being a pirate captain than simply steering the ship! Can you not see the open waters around us? Do you not taste the salt in the air, hear the gulls cry out skyward as we sail on? We are pirates, mon amie, pirates! We sail for glory, for riches, for lavish silks and the golden gleam of treasure!
          </text>
          <responses>
               <response>
                    (She yawns. He doesn’t seem to notice.)
               </response>
          </responses>
     </line>
     <line>
          <speaker>
               First Mate Bartholomew
          </speaker>
          <text>
               This majesty, this bold and fearsome spirit of adventure is something we must wield with pride -- and pride must carry a reputation. An image that conveys our raison d’etre, and frightens all who would dare challenge it! For my endeavors as captain to be successful, I must wear this pride with… er… with pride! Yes! Do you understand?
          </text>
          <responses>
               <response>
                    Hm? Oh, yeah, sure. (Please stop talking.)
               </response>
          </responses>
     </line>
     <line>
          <speaker>
               First Mate Bartholomew
          </speaker>
          <text>
               Excellent! With such disorder on our noble vessel, I had feared no one would hear my plight… but you are a gem among scoundrels, truly! I knew you would take my side.
          </text>
          <responses>
               <response>
                    That’s me. A dirty, rotten gem of a pirate.
               </response>
          </responses>
     </line>
     <line>
          <speaker>
               First Mate Bartholomew
          </speaker>
          <text>
               Now, for your first task as my dear assistant, you must help me become the very image of a true captain, one worthy of hanging on the hallowed halls of my future estate. I require a head of hair that commands authority, that speaks to my noble status on this ship. You must fetch me a wig. Surely you can find one here, can you not? Go ahead and get to it! Chop chop!
          </text>
          <responses>
               <response>
                    Okay
               </response>
          </responses>
     </line>
</dialogue>